<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KhabarovskTourGide</string>

    <string-array name="museums_name">
        <item>The Khabarovsk Regional Museum after N.I. Grodekov</item>
        <item>Military History Museum of the Far Eastern Military District</item>
        <item>Museum of The History of Amur Bridge</item>
        <item>Okladnikov Archaeology Museum</item>
        <item>Far Eastern Art Museum</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="museums_description">
        <item>It is the main museum of Khabarovsk, contains a lot of exhibitions worth to see. Museum was founded by N. I. Grodekov.
            The exposition devoted to paleontology and geology of the Amur River basin, flora and fauna, the Amur River fish,
            the culture of the indigenous peoples of the Amur and Slavs-settlers, the history and development of the Russian Far East,
            the events of the Civil War in the Far East of 1917-1922.</item>
        <item>The Military History Museum of Far Eastern Military District is located in an old building on the bank of the Amur River.
            Expositions of the military history museum number more than twelve thousand exhibits associated with the history from the time of its creation to our days.
            It contains a large number of military vehicles in the open air, which can easily climb.</item>
        <item>The museum is dedicated to the construction and reconstruction of the bridge over the Amur River near the city of Khabarovsk,
            in addition to the open air railway equipment is placed and the main exhibit of the museum is a dismantled farm of the "royal" bridge.</item>
        <item>Museum was opened in 1998. The museum is the only Far Eastern museum devoted entirely to the distant past of the Amur Region.
            The museum's funds hold over 120,000 ancient artifacts collected in expeditions of Khabarovsk, Novosibirsk and Vladivostok scientists.
            The pearl of the museum are the collections collected by Arseniev V.K. and Okladnikov A.P.</item>
        <item>It is the biggest Russian state-owned collection of the works art located in the western part ofPacific region.
            The Museum is located in the most picturesque place of Khabarovsk on the high bank of Amur river,
            occupying the building of former Officer Assembly.
            Thousands of Khabarovsk residents and multiple Russian and foreign guests of the city visit the Museum annually and enjoy the original old European and Russian paintings,
            antique ceramics, ancient Russian paintings, works of art by the Amur aboriginal and modern artists of the Russian far East.
            The collection exceeds now some 11000 exhibits. The Museum distinguished among the other museums of Russia for its broad exhibition activity.
            Museum exhibits its collections in other parts of Russia, represents the Russian Art in the galleries of Japan, Canada, the USA.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="museums_address">
        <item>Shevchenko St., 11</item>
        <item>Shevchenko St., 20</item>
        <item>Vokhr, 1A</item>
        <item>Turgeneva St., 86</item>
        <item>Shevchenko St., 7</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="museums_phone">
        <item>8 (421) 230-31-92</item>
        <item>8 (421) 232-63-50</item>
        <item>8 (421) 279-61-65</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>8 (421) 232-83-38</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="museums_sight">
        <item>http://www.hkm.ru</item>
        <item>http://www.artillery-museum.ru</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>http://www.двхм.рф</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="museums_photo">
        <item>grodekov_museum</item>
        <item>military_history_museum</item>
        <item>museum_of_the_history_of_amur_bridge</item>
        <item>okladnikov_archaeology_museum</item>
        <item>far_eastern_art_museum</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="cafe_name">
        <item>Signor Pomidor</item>
        <item>Le Nouage</item>
        <item>Vdrova</item>
        <item>Iron Kabis</item>
        <item>Meet Meat</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cafe_description">
        <item>One of the first and, perhaps, the best network of pizzerias in Khabarovsk. Dishes and salads are beyond praise. I recommend "Callabria" and "Capricious".</item>
        <item>Author's confectionery with the most amazing macaroons.</item>
        <item>Theme café with an atmosphere of Italian fairy tales and with a decent cuisine. Scream "Mama Mia" to call the waiter.</item>
        <item>Ossetian pies, homemade wine and beer. Cozy warm atmosphere of the Caucasian feast.</item>
        <item>The restaurant will definitely appeal to lovers of steaks</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cafe_address">
        <item>Lenina St., 53</item>
        <item>Komsomolskaya St., 79</item>
        <item>Muraviev Amursky St., 15</item>
        <item>Amur boulevard 56A</item>
        <item>Muraviev Amursky St., 5</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cafe_phone">
        <item>8 (421) 235-27-27</item>
        <item>8 (924) 404-04-89</item>
        <item>8 (421) 294-21-11</item>
        <item>8 (421) 245-17-71</item>
        <item>8 (962) 502-02-30</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cafe_site">
        <item>http://www.spomidor.ru/</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>empty</item>
        <item>http://www.ironkabis.ru/</item>
        <item>empty</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cafe_photo">
        <item>signor_pomidor</item>
        <item>le_nouage</item>
        <item>vdrova</item>
        <item>iron_kabis</item>
        <item>meet_meat</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


</resources>
